Trevor is an angry young man.
Made in Britain is a tv movie, crime, drama film directed by Alan Clarke.
After being sent to a detention centre, a teenage skinhead clashes with the
social workers who want to conform him to the status quo.
Trevor, played by Tim Roth.
Errol Dupray, played by Terry Richards.
Peter Clive, played by Bill Stewart.
Harry Parker, played by Eric Richard.
Superintendent, played by Geoffrey Hutchings.
Barry Giller, played by Sean Chapman.
Made in Britain is a (made in 1982), 1983 release, British television
play written by David Leland and directed by Alan Clarke.
It follows a 16-year-old racist skinhead and his constant
confrontations with authority figures.
It was broadcast on ITV on 10 July 1983 as the fourth in an untitled series of works by Leland (including Birth of a Nation), about
different aspects of the British educational system, which subsequently acquired the overall title of Tales Out of School.
It marked Tim Roth's television debut.
The film explores themes of prison, skinhead, police, authority, racist.
The tone is emotional.